<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Everything is social</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/zh/</link><description>Recent content on Everything is social</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:28:05 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/clientes/stik_web/zh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/zh/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:28:05 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/zh/contact/</guid><description> We’d love to hear from you how do I love STIK? let me count the ways. If you have any questions, or would let us know how you want to feel about Stik, go ahead and shoot us a message! We are all ears! info(at)stik.world Name Email Phone Comment Accept our Privacy and Terms Comment sent Comment can&amp;#39;t be sent Send * All fields required</description></item><item><title>法律咨询</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/zh/legal-advice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 13:28:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/zh/legal-advice/</guid><description>法律咨询 一般信息 Jeek 是一家西班牙贸易公司，注册地为Jeek ，CIF为V78946565， 在旧金山商业登记处|||，对开250，页码XA8794764。
https://stik.world是Jeek 拥有的Internet域，其中包含页面或 他 通过URL http：//https：//stik.world访问的网站。一般的联系方式是 电子邮件地址lega@stik.world和电话（+34）+005467889756。 当前条件的目的 这些一般条款规定了对Jeek Inc网站的访问和使用。 访问本网站，同意随时受现行通用条款的约束 任何。 如果您不同意本法律声明中包含的任何条件，则必须停止使用 Jeek Inc ..网站。
Jeek 保留随时修改本产品的权利，恕不另行通知。 当下 可能在任何时候建立的一般条件或特殊条件 一些特定的内容。
网站的使用 网站http：////https：//stik.world-以下简称本网站-将免费提供，而不会影响 每个用户必须支持的通过相应电信网络的连接 访问它。
用户了解并自愿并明确接受在任何情况下均根据以下规定使用本网站 您的唯一责任。
使用“网站”时，用户同意不进行任何可能损坏用户的行为。 的 Jeek 或第三方的图像，利益和权利，或可能损坏，超载，减少或 防止 如果使用户有可能反思站点评论或 做出任何形式的捐款，Jeek 保留立即撤回款项的权利 评论或贡献，如果您认为它们具有歧视性，仇外心理，种族主义，色情或 以任何方式侵犯对人的尊严的尊重，侵犯童年，秩序或 公共安全或他认为不适合公开发表的信息。
网站的安全性和免责声明 Jeek 采取了适当的安全措施以检测病毒的存在。不 然而， Jeek 无法保证其安全系统的绝对无害性，因此不包括 由于存在以下原因而导致的任何形式的损害的任何类型的责任 可能引起计算机系统（软件和硬件）变更的病毒或其他元素， 用户或任何第三方的电子文档和文件
Jeek 对通信中可能发生的故障不承担任何责任，也不保证 网站的可用性和连续性，也可能没有中断或 访问网站或其内容时出错。
Jeek 对用户通过可能的论坛，聊天或 在网站上启用的其他参与工具。
目录 该站点提供对可用的信息，服务或程序（“内容”）的访问 由Jeek 提供的用户。
Jeek 保留随时修改本产品的权利，恕不另行通知。 演示文稿，配置和网站内容。
用户同意根据法律和本法律声明使用内容 怎么样 以及其他可能适用于每种情况的其他条件，规定和说明 时刻。 数据收集格式 通过本网站提供给用户的某些服务的使用可能受到限制 至 先前完成相应的用户注册。</description></item><item><title>Explore ZH</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/zh/explore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:15:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/zh/explore/</guid><description>social.. Every thing is With , Stik is an all new social media app that converts objects, products and things into social networks! Scroll down to see how it works and what exciting things you can do with Stik. Everything is social. Stik is an all new social media app that converts objects, products and things into social networks! Scroll down to see how it works and what exciting things you can do with Stik.</description></item><item><title>Press room ZH</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/zh/press-room/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:15:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/zh/press-room/</guid><description> Press Room Every thing is Social. DOWNLOAD brand guide here DOWNLOAD STIK LOGO AND GLYPH</description></item><item><title>Reserved</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/zh/reserved/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:15:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/zh/reserved/</guid><description> Welcome
to Stik! Congratulations on becoming one of us! You’ll be one of the first to experience all the crazy stuff you’ll be able to do with the things around you! Now, how about corrupting some other people and making them one of us too? Social media is always better with friends! Share on:</description></item></channel></rss>