<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Everything is social</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/</link><description>Recent content on Everything is social</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:27:59 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/clientes/stik_web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:27:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/contact/</guid><description> We’d love to hear from you how do I love STIK? let me count the ways. If you have any questions, or would let us know how you want to feel about Stik, go ahead and shoot us a message! We are all ears! info(at)stik.world Name Email Phone Comment Accept our Privacy and Terms Comment sent Comment can&amp;#39;t be sent Send * All fields required</description></item><item><title>Legal advice</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/legal-advice/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 13:28:03 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/legal-advice/</guid><description>Legal advice GENERAL INFORMATION Stik is a Spanish trading company domiciled in Stik , with CIF V78946565 and Registered in the Mercantile Registry of San Francisco in Volume |||, folio 250, page number XA8794764. https://stik.world is an Internet domain owned by Stik and which contains the page or he website accessed via the URL https://stik.world. The general contact details are the email address lega@stik.world and telephone number (+34) +005467889756. PURPOSE OF THE PRESENT CONDITIONS These General Conditions regulate access to and use of the Stik Inc website.</description></item><item><title>Explore</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/explore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:15:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/explore/</guid><description>Every is With , Stik is an all new social media app that converts objects, products and things into social networks! Scroll down to see how it works and what exciting things you can do with Stik. social. thing Everything is social. Stik is an all new social media app that converts objects, products and things into social networks! Scroll down to see how it works and what exciting things you can do with Stik.</description></item><item><title>Press room</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/press-room/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:15:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/press-room/</guid><description> Press Room Every thing is Social. DOWNLOAD brand guide here DOWNLOAD STIK LOGO AND GLYPH</description></item><item><title>Username reserved</title><link>/clientes/stik_web/reserved/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 12:15:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>/clientes/stik_web/reserved/</guid><description> Welcome
to Stik! Congratulations on becoming one of us! You’ll be one of the first to experience all the crazy stuff you’ll be able to do with the things around you! Now, how about corrupting some other people and making them one of us too? Social media is always better with friends! Share on:</description></item></channel></rss>